Viewers all over the world, begin to reflect on God's mercy to you, to us.
God's mercy - unlimited.
Thank Him!
Thank Him for His mightiness!
Thank Him for His blessings!
Thank Him for His deliverance!
Thank Him for His healing!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command all unclean spirits operating in your life -
leave in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
All unclean spirits operating in your health - leave in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
They are the cause of sickness and disease.
All unclean spirits operating in your marriage -
leave, in the name of Jesus!
All unclean spirits operating in your career -
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank Jesus for His deliverance!
Thank Him for His deliverance!
I can see God's deliverance touching you!
I can see God's deliverance touching your health!
I can see God's deliverance touching your career!
I can see God's deliverance touching your marriage!
Give thanks to God for His deliverance!
Give thanks to Him!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray!
You can know if you are delivered.
I am saying, "You are delivered!"
You have been delivered!
I see you being delivered!
Tell your neighbour, "You can know if you are delivered".
God's Word says you can know.
You can know if you are delivered.
I know you are delivered, in Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I command healing on you, right now!
Jesus heals every infirmity.
Jesus heals every wound.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Give thanks to God for His healing.
I can see you being healed!
I can see God's healing touching you -
touching your blood, kidneys, liver, in the name of Jesus!
Give thanks to God!
The Lord is good.
Right now, ask God's grace to cover you!
In your life's journey, ask God's grace to cover you!
Ask God's grace to cover you,
in the name of Jesus Christ!
- I can't hear you.
- [Amen!]
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can hear breakthrough!
In all areas of your life, I can hear breakthrough!
Breakthrough!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You.
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
RV: Mel Flowers 07/04/2019